Guide to the Records and Papers of Terry Sanford, 1945-1998 UA.03.60.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series 1. Duke University. President Terry Sanford Records, 1969-1985.
  - Subseries 1.1. Subject files, 1969-1985, 175 ln. ft. (about 150,000 items
    - International Studies, Center for. Third WorldConvocation, 1985 February (Box 77)
    - Interns (Box 77)
    - Intramural Building, 1971 (Box 77)
    - Investments (Box 77)
    - Investor Responsibilty Research Center, Inc. (Box 77)
    - Invitations Accepted, 1970-1985, 8 folders (Box 78)
    - Invitations Declined, 1970-1972, 9 folders (Box 78)
    - Invitations, 1970-1973 (Box 78)
    - Invitations Declined, 1973-1979 A-M, 12 folders (Box 79)
    - Invitations Declined, 1979, N-Z - 1983, 9 folders (Box 80)
    - Invitations Declined, 1984-1985, 6 folders (Box 81)
    - Invitations Issued, 1980-1985 (Box 81)
    - Invitations List, [ 1970-1971], looseleaf volume (Box 81)
    - Islamic and Arabian Development Studies, 1977-1985, 4 folders (Box 81)
    - Italy Project (Box 81)
    - Ivey, Mrs. George M. (Box 81)
    - J. General correspondence, 1970-1979, 3 folders (Box 82)
    - Japan (Box 82)
    - Japan. Asian/Pacific Studies (Box 82)
    - Japan. Living History Program (Box 82)
    - Japan. Sasakawa, Ryoichi (Box 82)
    - Japan. Student Exchange. International Christian University (Box 82)
    - Japan. Trip, 1979 June 24-July 6 (Box 82)
    - Japan. United States-Japan Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 82)
    - Jargon [Society, Inc.] Papers, [1977-1979] (Box 82)
    - Jenkins, Kimberly (Box 82)
    - Jenkins, Leo W., Dr. [East Carolina University] (Box 82)
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, President. Library and School ofPublic Affairs (Box 82)
    - Journalism at Duke, 1971 (Box 82)
    - Judaic Studies, 1971-1984 (Box 82)
    - K. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 4 folders (Box 83)
    - Kaludis, George, Associates. 1984 Review of Senior Management (Box 83)
    - Kappa Delta Pi (Box 83)
    - Kelso, Louis. ESOPS. Draft of Social Capitalism... (Box 83)
    - Kennedy, K.D. (Box 83)
    - Kirby, Rebekah (Box 83)
    - Kissinger, Henry A., [1973-1978] (Box 83)
    - Kreps, Juanita. (Box 83)
    - Krueger, Robert, 1972-1975. Vice-Provost&Dean ofTrinity College of Arts and Sciences, U.S. Representative(TX) (Box 83)
    - L. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 6 folders (Box 83)
    - Ladd, Larry, 1974-1976 (Box 84)
    - Lamar Society, The L.Q.C. [1970-1978] (Box 84)
    - Law School, 1970-1985, 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Law School. Private Adjudication Center, Inc. (Box 84)
    - Law School. Van Alstyne, Prof. Wm. W. (Box 84)
    - Law School. Van Alstyne, Prof. Wm. W., brief for Dickson etal. vs. Sitterson et al. (Box 84)
    - Lewis, Harold. [Vice-Provost&Dean of the Faculty] (Box 84)
    - Library, 1970-1980, 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Library Council (Box 85)
    - Library of Congress. [Reading and Successful Living Conference, 1981] (Box 85)
    - Library, 1981-1985 (Box 85)
    - Library. Audio-Visual Center (Box 85)
    - Loblolly Performing Arts Program, 1976-1978 (Box 85)
    - Lord Corporation. Don Alstadt (Box 85)
    - Louis Harris and Associates, Inc., 1970 (Box 85)
    - M. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 7 folders (Box 85)
    - Mc. General correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 85)
    - MacLamroc, James G.W. (Box 86)
    - Management Improvement Corporation of America [Durham, N.C.; T.L. Amick] (Box 86)
    - Management Improvement Corporation of America. Robotics, 1980-1982. John Gallagher (Box 86)
    - Marshall, Roger, [ 1977-1984; Assistant to the President] (Box 86)
    - Martin Luther King Games, 1973 (Box 86)
    - Martin, Walker (Isobel Craven Young Martin [Drill]. Buck Young Foundation), [1967-1985] (Box 86)
    - Master of Arts in Liberal Studies (Box 86)
    - Mc. General correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 86)
    - McGovern, George (Box 86)
    - McKay, Martha (Box 86)
    - McKissick, Floyd B., 1974 (Box 86)
    - McLean, Malcolm P. (Cancer research, etc., scholarship foundation proposal, etc.) (Box 86)
    - Media Center and Audio-Visual Communications Development. (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Advisory board (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Alumni Weekend (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Anatomy Department (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Anlyan, William G., Dr., 1965-1985, 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Anlyan, William G., Dr., Interim Report, 1983 (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Bylaws of the Medical Staff (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Capitation Grants to Medical School (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Celebrity Golf Tournament (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Commonwealth Fund. Proposals (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Community and Family Medicine (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Complaints and Compliments, 1972-1980 (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Comprehensive Cancer Center (Box 86)
    - Medical Center. Complaints and Compliments, 1981-1982 (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Complaints and Compliments, 1983-1985 (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Development (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Dietary Rehabilitation Clinic (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Executive Health Examinations (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Eye Center, 1971- (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Highland Hospital, 1963-1982, 3 folders (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Highland Hospital. Advisory Committee (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Highland Hospital. Interview, CBS Sixty Minutes, Sept. 23, 1980 (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Hospital North, 1970-1978, 4 folders (Box 87)
    - Medical Center. Hospital North, 1980-1985 (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Hospital North, Dedication, 1980-1981 (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Hospital North. Financing Backstop Agreement, 1982 (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Hospital South. Planning (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Hyperbaric Chamber (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Jones, Edwin L., Cancer Research Center (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. May, Cordelia Scaife. Chair of Reproductive Biology and Family Planning, Endowment (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Medicaid Program [Funding Cuts], 1981 (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Medical Affairs Committee of the Board ofTrustees (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Miscellaneous, 1968-1985, 3 folders (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Modernization and Expansion Project. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Morris, Edwin A., Clinical Cancer Research Building. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Nursing, School of (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Nursing, School of. Report to the Board of Trustees, 1976. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Physical Therapy Program (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Physicians' Assistant Program (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Sea Level Hospital (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Symposium, 1977. The Future of the Private Sector (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. System for Hospital Uniform Reporting (SHUR) Legislation. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Thomas, John. Duke Retirement Community Proposal. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Wallace, Andrew G. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Walters, R.C. (Bucky) (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. Woodhall, Barnes. (Box 88)
    - Medical Center. [Mount Sinai Report, 1980] (Box 88)
    - Methodist Church (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Board of Higher Education and Ministry, 1970-1985, 3 folders (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Duke's Relationship with, 1964- (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Faculty Salaries (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. National Association of Schools and Colleges ofthe United Methodist Church, 1977-1985 (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. National Commission on United Methodist Higher Education. (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. North Carolina Conference, 1964-1985 (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Presidents of Methodist-related Universities, 1964- (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Southeastern Jurisdictional Conference (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Tuition at Duke. (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Undergraduate Curriculum Study, Grant for, 1966-1968 (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. University Senate, 1961- (Box 89)
    - Methodist Church. Western North Carolina Conference, 1964- (Box 89)
    - Methodist College. 1965-1976, 4 folders (Box 90)
    - Methodist College. President Search Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 90)
    - Methodist Ministers, Letters from (Box 90)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 1976 (Box 90)
    - Microelectronics Center of North Carolina, 1980-1984 (Box 90)
    - Mimms, Christine. Memos, notes and correspondence (Box 90)
    - Minister to the University, 1973-1983. Young, Robert T., 3 folders (Box 90)
    - Minister to the University, Acting. Kammerer, Charlene P. (Box 90)
    - Minister to the University. 1983-. Willimon, William H. (Box 90)
    - Minority Affairs (Box 90)
    - Missouri, University of. John C. Weaver. 1970 (Box 90)
    - Mitsubishi (Box 90)
    - Moffatt, Curtis (Box 90)
    - Mondale, [Walter] Fritz. (Box 90)
    - Morrison Award (Box 90)
    - Murdock, David H. (Box 90)
    - N. Correspondence, 1970-1985, 4 folders (Box 91)
    - Nance, Thurman F. / Jordan Lake / Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers' Association (Box 91)
    - Nathans, Elizabeth S., Dean (Box 91)
    - National ... [miscellaneous organizations] (Box 91)
    - National Academy of Public Administration, 1970-1982, 4 folders (Box 91)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1971-1984 (Box 91)
    - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), [1975-1983] (Box 91)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976-1984, 3 folders (Box 91)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 92)
    - National Board on Graduate Education, [1972-1976], 5 folders (Box 92)
    - National Book Committee, [1971-1974] (Box 92)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. (Box 92)
    - National Business Consortium for the Gifted and Talented (Box 92)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1970-1985, 4 folders (Box 93)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education, 1976-1985, 5 folders (Box 93)
    - National Committee for Support of the Public Schools, [1970-1973] (Box 93)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, [1971-1981] (Box 93)
    - National Congress on Church-Related Colleges and Universities, 1978-1979 (Box 93)
    - National Congress on Church-Related Colleges and Universities, 1979-1980 (Box 94)
    - National Council for Soviet and East European Research, 1977-1981 (Box 94)
    - National Council of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1970-[1976] (Box 94)
    - National Defense Education Act, 1970-1971 (Box 94)
    - National Driving Center, 1971- (Box 94)
    - National Education Association, [1971-1979] (Box 94)
    - National Electron Accelerator Laboratory, [1980-1981] (Box 94)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 94)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, [1972-1982] (Box 94)
    - National Governors' Association (Box 94)
    - National Humanities Center, 1975-1978 [see also Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies] (Box 94)
    - National Humanities Center, 1979-1985, 4 folders (Box 95)
    - National Institute of Ecology, [1970-1971] (Box 95)
    - National Labor Relations Board. See: Unions, Non-Academic Employees (Box 95)
    - National Research Council [see also National Board on Graduate Education] (Box 95)
    - National Science Foundation, 1970-1984, 3 folders (Box 95)
    - National Urban Coalition. See: Urban America, Inc. (Box 95)
    - Nature Conservancy, [1977-1983] (Box 95)
    - Naval Academy Foreign Affairs Conference, [1973] (Box 95)
    - Naylor, Thomas H. (Box 95)
    - Neuharth, Allen H. [Gannett Co.] (Box 95)
    - New Orleans [Moon Landrieu, Mayor] (Box 95)
    - New York Concert. March 19, 1977. Carnegie Hall. Duke Choir and Chorale with the N.C. Symphony Orchestra (Box 95)
    - New York Times Supplement, 1973, October 7. [Duke University supplement] (Box 95)
    - New York Times, 1970, November 17. Agnew article (Box 95)
    - Newsome, C.G., Acting Dean of Black Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 95)
    - Nixon Library. Academic Council (Weintraub) [1981 Aug-Oct] (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Academic Council from [Board of Trustees] Executive Committee, Sept. 5, [1981] (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Advisory and Negotiating Committees (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Alumni Letters, 1981-1982 (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Applicants (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Cartoon. Dwane Powell, News and Observer, August 16, 1981 (see box 229) (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Clippings, 3 folders (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Departments, Groups, Schools, etc. Correspondence (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Duke Faculty from R. Marshall (Resolution). Sept. 4, [1981] (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Faculty Letters (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Faculty and Emeriti Faculty. No (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Faculty and Emeriti Faculty. Yes (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Faculty. Non-committal and Misc. Correspondence (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Goodwin, Craufurd. Correspondence, 1981 (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Green, William L., Correspondence, 1981 (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. IBM 5220 diskette containing correspondence typed by Pam Blake re. Nixon Library, 1981 (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Letters to Board of Trustees after September 4, 1981 (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Letters to Board with copies to TS. No (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Letters to Board with copies to TS. Yes (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Letters to TS enclosing letters to the Board. No (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Letters to TS enclosing letters to the Board. Yes (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. McDonald, [Eugene], correspondence (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. McMahon, [J. Alexander], correspondence (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. [Academic Council Meeting, 1981 August 31] (Box 96)
    - Nixon, President Richard (& White House) (Box 96)
    - Nixon, Richard M., Scholarship, 1973- (Box 96)
    - Nixon Library. Marshall, Roger (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Marshall, [Roger. Statement concerning the proposed...] October 11, [1981] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Mattie Russell and Bill King. Correspondence (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Miscellaneous (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Miscellaneous correspondence, 4 folders (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Mortenson, [Stan] and Warner, [Robert M.] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Murphy, [Charles S.] correspondence (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Pye, [Kenneth], correspondence. (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Rhyne, [Charles S.], correspondence (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Student letters - no (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Student letters - yes (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] Memo to Academic Council, Aug. 19, [1981] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] Memo to Alumni and Students, Aug. 18, [1981] (Cady letter) (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] Memo to Board of Trustees, Aug. 15, [1981] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] Memo to Executive Committee, Aug. 8, [1981] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] Memo to Faculty, Sept. 2, [1981] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. T[erry] S[anford] to Board of Trustees. Sydney Nathans' materials. (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Trustee letters - no (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Trustee letters - non-committal (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Trustee letters - yes (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Unfoldered materials (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Unsigned or no address (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. [Reese, Morris G.] (Box 97)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni- yes, 12 folders (Box 98)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni - no, 6 folders (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni and others (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni, with clippings. (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni. Duplicates/copies (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from alumni. Unsorted (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from others - no (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters from others - yes (Box 99)
    - Nixon Library. Letters. Unsorted (Box 99)
    - Non-academic Employees (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Academy of Science, 1972-1979 (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Advancement School (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Association of Black Educators (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Association of Educators, Inc. (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1970-1979, 10 folders (Box 100)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1980-1985, 5 folders (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges andUniversities. Legislation (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities. North Carolina Constitutional Ammendment V, 1982 (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities. Public Support of Private Higher Education: Comments of Sanford to Joint Committee on Higher Education, 1977 May 10 (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities. Council of Trustees, 1977-1981 (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities. Smith vs. Board of Governors of UNC (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Awards, 1970-1984, 4 folders (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Biotechnology Center (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Boys' State (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Center for Independent Higher Education, Inc., 1977 (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Center for Public Policy Research (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Central University (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Child Advocacy Institute (Box 101)
    - North Carolina Community College and Technical Institute Planning Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Community Colleges and Technical Institutes (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Community Colleges, 1978-1981 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Administration (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Administration. Council on the Status of Women, 1978-1980, 3 folders (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Administration. Human Relations Council (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Agriculture. Jim Graham (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Archives and History (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Commerce (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Crime Control and Public Safety (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Cultural Resources (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Human Resources (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Natural and Economic Resources (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Department of Public Instruction (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Film Board (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Fund (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Governor's School (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Governor. James B. Hunt, 1974-1984 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Governor. James E. Holshouser, 1973-1977 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Governor. James G. Martin III (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Governor. Robert W. Scott, 1969-1977 (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Gubernatorial Succession Amendment (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Heart Association [concerning University policy on solicitation] (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Highway Patrol (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Institute of Government (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Institute of Politics (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Internship Office (Box 102)
    - North Carolina Learning Institute of North Carolina, 1965-1979, 12 folders (Box 103)
    - North Carolina Legislative Study Commission on Student Financial Aid (Box 103)
    - North Carolina Legislative Tuition Grants (Box 103)
    - North Carolina Legislative Tuition Grants. Thank-you letters from students (Box 103)
    - North Carolina Legislature, 1970-1985, 3 folders (Box 103)
    - North Carolina Miscellaneous, 1970-1984 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Museum of Art (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Museum of Life and Science (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Outward Bound School, 1981-1983, 5 folders (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Press Association Award (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Public Interest Research Group (NCPIRG), 1973-1977 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics, 1968-1985 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1970-1985 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Science and Technology Task Force, 1973, 1982-1984 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina Sports Facility (Box 104)
    - North Carolina State Aid to Higher Education, 1970-1973 (Box 104)
    - North Carolina State Aid to Higher Education Paid Through the University of North Carolina, 1973- (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State Aid to Higher Education, 1974-1980, 3 folders (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State Commission on Higher Education Facilities (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State Government Reorganization. Governor's Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State Highway Commission (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State Student Legislature (Box 105)
    - North Carolina State University (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Symphony (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Wesleyan College (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Writers' Conference (Box 105)
    - North Carolina Zoological Park (Box 105)
    - North Carolina. University of North Carolina Advisory Council of Private Colleges and Universities to the UNC Board of Governors (Box 105)
    - North Carolina. University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1970-1985, 4 folders (Box 105)
    - North Carolina. University of North Carolina at Charlotte (Box 105)
    - North Carolina. University of North Carolina. Tom Lambeth&Ray Farris. [re: relationship with private institutions and public support for independent higher education] (Box 105)
    - North Carolina. Videotapes. Ralph Scott, etc. Interviews (Box 105)
    - O. General correspondence, 1968-1985, 3 folders (Box 106)
    - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, [1970-1983] (Box 106)
    - Occupational Forecasting, Inc., 1981 (Box 106)
    - Olive, B.B., 1972-1984 [Patents; Duke Forest] (Box 106)
    - Operation Breakthrough, [1969-1983] (Box 106)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1970-1985 (Box 106)
    - Orr, [Louis] Etchings, [1981-1982] (Box 106)
    - Ossabaw Island, [Georgia, 1964-1977] (Box 106)
    - Overton, Dolph, [1979] (Box 106)
    - P. General correspondence, 1970-1985, 8 folders (Box 106)
    - Palm Beach Conference Center, 1978 [Mar-A-Lago, M.M. Post home] (Box 106)
    - Pan-Africa Track Meet, 1971 (Box 106)
    - Pan-Africa, West Germany, USA International Track and Field Meet, 1975 (Box 106)
    - Panama Canal [Treaty, 1977-1978] (Box 106)
    - Panel of American Women, [1976-1977] (Box 107)
    - Parents' Weekend, [1980-1984] (Box 107)
    - Patent Office, 1977-1985, 5 folders (Box 107)
    - Patterson, Eugene C., [1971-1972] (Box 107)
    - Patton, Vicky, 1970-1983 (Box 107)
    - Payroll Savings Plan, [1972-1983] (Box 107)
    - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell,&Company, 1964-1970 (Box 107)
    - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency Grants, 1970-1973 (Box 107)
    - Personal Assistance Service for Duke Employees and Families, [1984] (Box 107)
    - Personnel, 1973-1985, 10 folders (Box 107)
      [70 year restriction]
    - Pfeiffer College. Cameron West. 1978-1982 (Box 107)
    - Phelps, Jake, [1972-1983] (Box 107)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, [1972-1979] (Box 107)
    - Phytotron, [1977-1981] (Box 107)
    - Pinsky, Mark, [1970-1978] (Box 107)
    - Piva, John J., Jr. [1982-1985] [VP, Alumni Affairs andDevelopment] (Box 107)
    - Placement Office. [1964-1983]. Patricia O'Conner, Director (Box 107)
    - Poland (Box 107)
    - Political Science, Dept. of, [1971] [Ralph Braibanti] (Box 107)
    - Pratt, Ella Fountain. [1964-1984] (Box 107)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum, [Clippings and printed matter] (Box 107)
    - Presidential Awards, [1983-1985] (Box 107)
    - Presidential Nominations Forum (Box 107)